Do you think now
the Chinese have fallen
behind You know I
think they never really
caught up that much
you of there was
this huge excitement around
DeepSeek right But
you the truth was
a couple things One
you those models are
very optimized for the
benchmarks It's actually very
easy to a for
a list of When
we go out into
the right When we're
you know against
other companies for enterprise
contracts we see just
honestly and candidly we
see Google and we
see OpenAI Every once
in we see a
other US players
I have almost never
lost a deal a
contract to a Chinese
model But now you
have the administration and
I think you've already
protested about this giving
high speed chips and
video chips to the
Chinese That's right that's
right The thing that
is holding them back
and they've said it
The CEOs of these
companies say it's the
embargo on that's holding
us back They explicitly
say this